

SUMMARY

I have successfully finished Full Stack Web Developer course at Code Institute (Napier University), where I have built 4 websites using several different languages. This recently-finished web developer courses experience has shaped my code evaluation and website development knowledge, I have the HTML5, CSS, JavaScript and Python(Django) skills.

PERSONAL INFO

Address

Bournemouth, UK

Phone

+44 78894 52743

E-mail

michalwesolowski11@gmail.com

LinkedIn

@MichalWesolowski

Github

www.github.com/Michael0812

HOBBIES

- Playing football
- Love to travel around the world
- Ready to read about history
- Happy and relaxed after yoga

MICHAL WESOLOWSKI

Junior Full Stack Web Developer

EDUCATION

Code Institute (Napier University)

04/2019 - 06/2020

Second Class Honours (2:1) Diploma of Higher Education in Full Stack Web Developer

The Bournemouth & Poole College

03/2018 - 01/2019

A-Level or equivalent in C&G Level 1 Award in ESOL skills for Life (Writing, Reading, Speaking)

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

04/2019 - Present

Working as a freelancer and in cooperation with a Polka. Graphic Designs.

Sunseeker International Ltd - Laminator

04/2017 - 05/2019

Working on 76ft Super Yacht in Sunseeker.

Wet lay up and Infused (VARTM) components such as:

- Hulls
- Decks
- Superstructures

Lush Limited - Compounder

09/2014 - 04/2017

- Compound to the high standard
- Dealing safety with raw materials
- Use the fork lift when essential
- Send orders and unpack delivers

SKILLS

Languages:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python

Libraries and Frameworks:

- Django3
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Stripe
- Materialize
- Jinja
- Flask

Tools:

- Gitpod
- VScode
- AWS
- Travis
- Balsamiq
- AdobeXD

Database:

- PostgresSQL
- SQlite3
- MongoDB

Version Control:

- Git
- Github

PROJECTS

Black & White

Purpose for this project was to build ecommerce website.

Black & White it is webshop with coffee. This website contains a dozen products. The central target audience are clients who loved coffee, value good coffee and take care of environment. Stripe was used for payments method. The content of this website is for educational purposes only.

Ocean Pollution

This website is for everyone, however I was mainly aiming at young people who show interest, and would like to learn a bit more about ocean pollution and what to do to help with this issue.

I wanted people to take action. The content of this website is for educational purposes only.

Handy Crane

This is a one page website. Contains main information about the company and what they are offering for their customers along with a wide photo gallery of their products. This was a freelance project.

Mixerzzzz

This site is devoted to the world-famous whisky. The purpose of this page is not to provide extensive book definitions, but to explain what is best mixed with your favorite whisky. CRUD functions was used in this project.